

# **Sherri Scheer**

# Web Developer/UX Design

sherrischeer@icloud.com 314.610.4882

Portfolio: github.com/sherrischeer/portfolio www.sherrischeer.com

#### **PROFILE**

Hello! I am a self-motivated professional with experience in customer service and teamwork, who pays close attention to detail and making strong customer relationships. I have found my passion in the tech industry and would like to share it with others as well as utilize the skills I have obtained. I am very organized and detail-oriented. I love to learn and have a passion for accomplishment.

# **EDUCATION**

LaunchCode Codergirl – User Experience (UX) Summer Cohort, 2018

St. Louis Community College – Web Development Certificate, 2018

Current Trends Academy - St. Peters, MO – Licensed as Cosmetologist, 2009

National Academy of Beauty Arts - St. Louis, MO – Nail Technician, 1999

University of MO St Louis – BSBA – Bachelor of Science in Business Administration, emphasis in Marketing, 1989

# **PROFESSIONAL SKILL**

HTML5, CSS3 – websites and redesigns

JavaScript, jQuery – links, animations, timers, forms and data validation

UX/UI – went through the design process with Codergirl

Github, Bootstrap – my portfolio

Wordpress - my website

Photoshop – used on almost every project

Agile Methodology - studied this in Codergirl

## **EXPERIENCE**

Hairstyles by Sherri & Changes Salon & Spa.

My passion is to help people. I get to do this every day by helping them be beautiful and provide an easy way to maintain it. I build and maintain customer relationships by listening, customizing care and helping clients choose the best for their hair.

Sales Event Specialist, American Deli Products; St Louis, MO — 2016-2017

Promote Boar's Head products in supermarkets by sampling and offering product information to make life-long customers.

Administrative Assistant, Vineyard Christian Fellowship; St Louis, MO — 1994-1999 Accounting and Creative Team (bulletins, brochures, booklets, database, tax records)

Marketing Manager, Ocean Club; Southern CA — 1992-1994

Booked Banquets, handled all marketing ads, flyers, etc. Oversee promotions.

Account Representative, L'eggs Hosiery; Southern CA — 1991-1992

Travel to stores in Southern CA and Las Vegas. Inventory, order and deliver product. Update display merchandising. Report losses, etc.

## **INTERESTS**

I believe if you want to give more, you have to become more. That is why I believe in having fun and routine. My interests include family, fitness, reading, travel, and movie night. I serve at church in the coffee-bar and on the Summit High School lacrosse board as Co-President in training.